kimchidrama.blogspot.com 2012-01-29

# Privacy Policy | KimchiDrama

* Kimchidramas.net Privacy Policy

Kimchidramas.net is committed to protecting your privacy. Kimchidramas.net does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. Kimchidramas.net will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. The following contains details on how we treat all information collected on Kimchidramas.net

* Your Acceptance

BY USING AND/OR VISITING THIS WEBSITE (collectively, including all Content available through the Kimchidramas.net domain name, the "KimchiDrama Website", or "Website"), YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO TERMS OF USE, WHICH ARE PUBLISHED AT http://www.kimchidramas.net/p/privacy-policy.html, AND WHICH ARE INCORPORATED HEREIN BY REFERENCE. If you do not agree to any of these terms, then please do not use the Kimchidramas.net Website.

* All Users Activity

Any User can use Kimchidramas.net without having a Kimchidramas.net Account or any other Account.

* Usage Information

We may record information about your usage, such as when you use Kimchidramas.net, how many times you visit the website and other non-personal identifiable information.

* Uses

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through Kimchidramas.net, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of Kimchidramas.net, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Kimchidramas.net changes).

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of Kimchidramas.net and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.

Any link that you voluntarily send us becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

* Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

Kimchidramas.net allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within Kimchidramas.net. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on Kimchidramas.net. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

Kimchidramas.net does not provide any personally identifiable information to third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.
